

# **HASSAM SALEEM**

Full Stack Developer

# **RESUME OBJECTIVE**

Software Developer with 2+ years of experience in Web and Desktop App Development. I have strong hand on different types of systems (listed in Projects Section). I seek a full-time position in the related field of Software world, where I can apply and enhance my knowledge and skills for continuous improvement.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **DOT NET/PHP DEVELOPER**

# GrizzlyAtoms LLC | Mar 2020 - Ongoing

 Working at GrizzlyAtoms LLC (U.S.A based company) as a Web App Developer and Scraping Incharge.

# **DOT NET/PHP DEVELOPER**

# SofticEra Faisalabad | Aug 2019 - Mar 2020

• Worked at SofticEra as a Web/Desktop App Developer for 7-months duration.

#### **WEB & DESKTOP APP DEVELOPER**

# Zee Solution Faisalabad | Sept 2018 - Aug 2019

 Worked at Zee Solution as a Web/Desktop App Developer for 11-months duration.

### **WEB CONTENT & ARTICLE WRITER**

# Axiom Solution Faisalabad | Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

• Worked as Web content & Article writer at Axiom Solution for 6-months duration.

# **WEB & DESKTOP APP DEVELOPER**

# UNIAL Solution Faisalabad | Sept 2017 - Dec 2017

 Worked as internee at UNIAL Solution for Web & Desktop App Development for 3-months duration.

## **PROJECTS**

- POS System
- Stock Management
- Inventory Management
- E-Commerce Websites
- CMS Systems
- Blockchain System
- Invoicing System
- Booking System

# **EDUCATION**

### **BS(HONS) IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY**

GC University, Faisalabad | 2014 - 2018

## INTERMEDIATE IN COMPUTER SCIENCES

Superior College, Faisalabad | 2012 - 2014

#### **CONTACTS**

Email: hassamsaleem55@gmail.com

Phone: +923070117297

Address: Faisalabad, Punjab Pakistan

### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- Web Development via PHP (Codelgniter) & ASP .NET with JQuery AJAX
- Desktop App Development via C# .Net
- SQL with Joins & Transactions
- HTML/CSS/Bootstrap
- Software Knowledge
  - o Visual Studio
  - Visual Code
  - Sublime
  - NetBeans
  - SQL Server
  - o HeidiSQL
  - Xampp
  - o Wamp
  - Microsoft Office (Word, Power Point, Excel)

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

- Reliable and professional
- Organized
- Time management
- Team player
- Fast Learner
- Motivated
- Good Internet Surfer